# **Alex Win**

## Director and Producer - Artébone

Philadelphia, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Alex-Win/9e5cbc09a835c2fa

I have 9+ years of video production and post-production experience. I am proficient and knowledgeable of industry standard video, audio, and lighting equipment and techniques. I have produced and edited numerous info-tainment videos and content for companies such as; Demand Media, Loreal, Home Depot, and Rachel Ray.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Director and Producer**

Artébone - Philadelphia, PA - July 2008 to Present

Artébone is a media collective specializing in original video content for commercial clients and artists alike. Directed and produced content for: SXSW Austin music showcase, Musa Fashion

Co. (Japan), Red Bull, PAU WAU Records, Wild Child, American Sharks, Gracie Brazilian

Jiu-Jitsu Academy, Alicia Keys, Fools Gold Records, Grande Marshall, GWAR, and many more.

## **Senior Content Producer**

Oogeewoogee.com - Philadelphia, PA - May 2015 to January 2016

Responsible for producing and maintaining video content for the website and Facebook.

Collaborated with internal creative team and journalists to produce video, text and photo content into meaningful digital stories. Supervised all aspects of video production from ideation to exporting. Handled tasks of restructuring video and media workflow from scratch.

Managed the archiving of past video content for future access.

# **Video Producer and Technical Assistant**

Artébone - Philadelphia, PA - October 2011 to April 2014

Developed video pieces and concept strategies for internationally renowned artist Terry

Adkins. Responsible for archiving past video pieces and performances, video editing, and digital distribution for exhibition in spaces such as Frieze Art Fair, Salon 94, Tate Modern,

Tang Museum, and other international institutions and galleries.

#### Freelance Editor and Jr. Producer

Artébone - Austin, TX - October 2010 to September 2011

Worked with senior producers to produce, edit, and distribute commercial video content and web series. Clients included: Ehow, Livestrong, Loreal, Rachel Ray, Terminix, and Home

Depot. Assisted in creating massive archive of stock footage for commercial use.

#### **EDUCATION**

# MFA

University of Pennsylvania - Philadelphia, PA 2011 to 2013

# **Bachelor of Fine Arts in Photography and Digital Media**

University of Houston - Houston, TX 2004 to 2008

# **SKILLS**

Adobe Premier Pro (5 years), After Effects (9 years), Final Cut Pro Professional Suite (10+ years), Adobe Creative Suite (10+ years), Canon Mark iii (4 years), Red Epic 4k Camera (3 years), Experience in directing, producing and editing video content for high-end clients (7 years)

LINKS

http://www.artebone.com